I will go without disturbing the units, because they are quite sensitive.
These chairs here that you have moved on and pushed down on the floor even, could you be able to get them to move a little neighbor only when we stand here?
I have one thing in my hand that you can come up and talk ...
The man who is here, if I'm talking to you right now ...
Can you say your name to us?
We can test anyway, we know Arne, his brother perished in a fire a year and a half ago here in Säffle.
That's when these things started to happen.
And I think he mentioned that his name was Tommy.
Okay.
So Tommy, if you are in this apartment ...
And want to say something to Arne, greet him something.
So you have the opportunity to do it now.
If you are Tommy who is here, can you go to the table here and touch the antenna?
Or just go by and we'll see that you're here.
I put it over there.
Do you see the two lamps lying and pulsating here?
If you put your hand on one of these pages, it will shine a color.
So we can talk to you, you walking around here.
That knocks in the walls.
You are quiet because you want to listen too, in case you hear these the banks.
Not only that, they have had power under the bed when they sleep.
Like someone lying and scratching on the floor.
So all sounds are very important here now.
Do you like when knocking in the walls here?
Maybe we should look out of another theory ..
There may be something with the ground.
That it is not linked to the family but there is something below?
The strange thing is that they have lived here for 13 years, but this started about a year and a half ago, when his brother passed away.
Is there anything in the ground here?
Has something happened in this place?
I get a lot with digs.
That's what I mean.
And Find Ashes.
What does it mean?
Is there anything under this apartment?
Finish what?
You may attack me when I'm here.
Pull in this bed and make it shake so I want to get up from here.
You don't have to be afraid of me, Niclas or Viktor who is in here now.
Without doing what you usually do when the others, Eva and Arne are here.
No vibrations here.
Statical field here!
Thanks!
Can you do it again?
Damn it fast.
Were you here with me exactly?
It was a woman.
"Yes"
Here?
Is it a child who is here?
Have you died in this place?
Is your ashes under this house?
"Running"
Spring sounded like.
We will not run from here.
Can you push out a chair to us are you kind?
"Hå **** t!"
It starts here, it shines!
Come come!
I think we got it on surveillance.
Shone the pyramid?
Both static and REM function went.
Both?
Just as we went out and I turned around, they started glowing.
Good, follow us out here then.
So we go to the kitchen so we can talk to you there.
It is typical that it is after that it is in the room where we leave.
Yes.
You who have talked to us before, can you come in and talk to us again?
Say yes if it is.
"Yes"
It's something else.
"Strong"
Are you buried under this house?
Is your ash under this house?
Lennie, have you looked up anything about the place?
Yes, I have found that there is an old pilgrim trail outside here.
Could it be true?
Yes, it's a joint.
It's a joint here?
Okay.
Is there anything more you've got about the place?
No more than there is a cemetery about one, one and a half kilometers away.
That's right.
It is out after the narrow road.
Thanks Lennie, great.
That's what we've been up to now, we get this with ash, legs, digs and now you asked if it is in the ground.
Then maybe we have a line to go on, that it is not linked to you in this case, but there is something near here.
But if there is something in the ground ..
who want to remind themselves that they are here ...
Can you touch something in here?
Have you followed any object in this building here?
I actually get a first contact here.
And then I see as a figure of an older gentleman sitting in that armchair.
He sits just like the armchair is directed, so he sits and stare straight in like this, in the TV.
He is here to keep track and wants to be close to you.
So I connect that there is a relative.
He wants to keep track and he sits here and just wants it to be calm and well for you.
And he has a fairly clear energy and he shows that he has tried to contact you by affecting the electronics.
That he has hit the TV or raised the sound and the like.
And turns on the TV at night ..
I'll try to see how he ... I'll move a little here.
I'll know what kind of relatives this might be.
I get a name, it doesn't have to be this name, it can be similar.
And I hear Arne ... It may be that the letters A and R are in the name.
But it is Arne anyway.
And he feels a little older, about 80 years, as he shows up.
And I connect him a lot to you, that it is you that he simply belongs to that it is you he wants to be close.
But he is a good energy.
He says he knows you know about him, that you have felt his energy here.
And especially right here on the couch.
For example, if you have been here yourself on the couch, you have felt that you are not really alone.
And it is not intended to be intimidated, he says, but he just wants to show his presence.
By pure love.
But what you can do then, what I do with relatives and those who are friendly and are just here of love, it is that he tones them down a bit.
But I don't completely remove them if there are family bands.
I think I want to move on a little first, then we go back here in case he wants to show me something more.
Then I want to go in here.
Here I get a woman pretty quickly.
And this woman belongs to you.
She shows that she stands against the wardrobe and folds together and folds the sheet.
It should be nice and it is so important to her.
Brother.
Okay.
And he was pretty messy.
But I'm trying to tone him away.
Since it is a relative, I do not completely remove, but it will be very quiet when he disappears.
And I do it at once now.
So that we can continue in the rest of the house, otherwise he will disturb all the time.
I'll see if he has any last message to say.
The last message is to you then.
It is that you should think about the posture, not just for back problems but you should show that you are a man, you can do this.
You should be straight -backed.
He says that you should not be a look and go like this, but now you can show that you are the man here.
That you take over after me now he says.
So that's his message to you.
Are you okay with me tone him away a bit?
Yes.
That's good.
Then I'll bring in some light and angels here.
That's how.
I saw him go away and I showed the light and explained that there is no hell but he will get help there on the other side.
And get the love he needs.
He has also received his message through and has shown that it is he who has been here simply.
So hopefully it will be much calmer, just the passive and intense energy.
I actually felt the scrub there, I feel an energy that is hiding.
As soon as I come, it's like the energy is behind something.
Which is a bit shy.
It is a little boy that I get in, who is about this long.
Very mischievous.
And as soon as there is a medial person here, because he feels that I can communicate, then he starts and buses.
So that's why he hides and runs around here.
And this boy is a little lost, because he is looking for his parents.
He has not really switched to the light.
I need to get them to meet each other, so he is led into the light.
He has run here very much on weekdays, back and forth.
I hear in my head that you have heard these little running.
And he likes to re -furnish in the shelves and roll stuff and that's because he is busing.
When I ask about how he died, I feel fire smoke.
It may have been like he has burned inside or that he has been burned in some way.
Because I feel a lot of fire smoke around him and then he shows burns on the body.
I removed there, then we had the energy here too that I should try to tone down.
So now I will really just go around where we have been.
Our expectations of the house in Säffle were high.
After everything the family told, documented and experienced.
What if we would witness a powerful poltergeist phenomenon for the first time?
Which even had such power to be able to punch holes in walls.
It was interesting to see how the medium Wilma worked.
She got a lot that agreed to Arne's brother Tommy, who tragically died in a fire.
It will be interesting to see if it has been calm after Wilma helps the energies over to the other side.
But the question is whether it has become completely calm?
Or if the forces that remain in the house that cause the phenomenon appear to have switched to the other side.
Or lies dormant to get back with full force.